rankevo.com 2017-06-02

# Privacy Policy - RankEvo

Privacy Policy for rankevo.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at rankevo@mail.com.

At rankevo.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance. This privacy policy outlines the type of personal information that is received and collected by rankevo.com and how it is used.

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, rankevo.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites. Cookies are used by most websites to tailor content and marketing messages to better suit your needs.

We use cookies on the website to track visitor behavior. If you prefer not to allow the use of cookies, you can change the configuration of your browser to warn you when you receive a cookie or automatically reject them.

If you would like to find out more about cookies you can visit [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

### Types of cookie used

**Google Analytics** – We use Google Analytics to understand how the website is being used in order to improve the user experience. User data is anonymous.

**Google Remarketing** — Google uses these cookies to show relevant adverts to users who have previously visited our website, as they browse other websites. You can opt-out from Google’s remarketing program, by changing your [](https://www.google.com/settings/ads)Google Ad Settings.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on rankevo.com.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to rankevo.com and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Advertising partners include…   
Google Adsense  

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on rankevo.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

rankevo.com uses Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using Google’s [Ad Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) page. Users can completely block Google Analytics tracking using [Google’s Analytics Opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. rankevo.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
